<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TugasDay06</string>
    <string name="kaguya">The elite members of Shuchiin Academy s student council continue their competitive day-to-day antics. Council president Miyuki Shirogane clashes daily against vice-president Kaguya Shinomiya, each fighting tooth and nail to trick the other into confessing their romantic love. Kaguya struggles within the strict confines of her wealthy, uptight family, rebelling against her cold default demeanor as she warms to Shirogane and the rest of her friends. Meanwhile, council treasurer Yuu Ishigami suffers under the weight of his hopeless crush on Tsubame Koyasu, a popular upperclassman who helps to instill a new confidence in him. Miko Iino, the newest student council member, grows closer to the rule-breaking Ishigami while striving to overcome her own authoritarian moral code. As love further blooms at Shuchiin Academy, the student council officers drag their outsider friends into increasingly comedic conflicts.</string>
    <string name="sou">Selama pencarian selama satu dekade mereka untuk mengalahkan Raja Iblis, anggota partai pahlawan—Himmel sendiri, pendeta Heiter, prajurit kurcaci Eisen, dan penyihir elf Frieren—membangun ikatan melalui petualangan dan pertempuran, menciptakan kenangan berharga yang tak terlupakan bagi sebagian besar dari mereka. Namun, waktu yang dihabiskan Frieren bersama kawan-kawannya hanya sebagian kecil dari hidupnya, yang telah berlangsung lebih dari seribu tahun. Ketika partai tersebut bubar setelah kemenangan mereka, Frieren dengan santainya kembali ke rutinitas "biasa" nya mengumpulkan sihir di seluruh benua. Karena persepsi waktunya yang berbeda, dia tampaknya tidak memiliki perasaan yang kuat terhadap pengalaman yang telah dia lalui. Seiring berjalannya waktu, Frieren secara perlahan menyadari betapa hari-harinya di partai pahlawan benar-benar memengaruhinya. Melihat kematian dua dari mantan teman-temannya, Frieren mulai menyesali telah menganggap keberadaan mereka sebagai hal yang biasa; dia bersumpah untuk lebih memahami manusia dan menciptakan hubungan personal yang nyata. Meskipun cerita perjalanan yang dulu mengesankan itu sudah berakhir lama, kisah baru akan segera dimulai.</string>
    <string name="mao">Maomao, an apothecarys daughter, has been plucked from her peaceful life and sold to the lowest echelons of the imperial court. Now merely a maid, Maomao settles into her new mundane life and hides her extensive knowledge of medicine in order to avoid any unwanted attention. Not long after Maomaos arrival, the emperors infant children inexplicably begin to experience grave symptoms—almost as if a curse has been cast. The curious Maomao easily solves the mystery and, to remain out of the limelight, attempts to leave an anonymous tip. Unfortunately, the dashing and perceptive eunuch Jinshi sees through it and manages to single her out. In recognition of her talent, Maomao is promoted to lady-in-waiting for the emperors favorite concubine, Gyokuyou. As Maomao continues to remedy the numerous ailments afflicting the imperial court, her pharmaceutical expertise quickly proves indispensable</string>
</resources>